* + [Clothing](https://www.owayo.com/productservice/products/apparel-us.htm)

* + [Head and neck](https://www.owayo.com/productservice/products/head-and-neck-us.htm)

* + [Merchandise](https://www.owayo.com/productservice/products/merchandise-us.htm)

* + [Strengths](https://www.owayo.com/productservice/mydesign-us.htm)

* + [Support](https://www.owayo.com/productservice/price_estimates-us.htm)

* + [About owayo](https://www.owayo.com/productservice/news-us.htm)

* + [Contact](https://www.owayo.com/productservice/contact-us.htm)

Shopping Cart

Your shopping cart is empty.

[My Account](#) [Log out of](#)   Log in

* more [Product Service](https://www.owayo.com/productservice-us.htm)

    * Continue to
    
* more [Products](https://www.owayo.com/productservice/products-us.htm)
    
    more [Clothing](https://www.owayo.com/productservice/products/apparel-us.htm)

    more [Head and neck](https://www.owayo.com/productservice/products/head-and-neck-us.htm)

    more [Merchandise](https://www.owayo.com/productservice/products/merchandise-us.htm)

* more [Strengths](https://www.owayo.com/productservice/mydesign-us.htm)

* more [Support](https://www.owayo.com/productservice/price_estimates-us.htm)

* more [About owayo](https://www.owayo.com/productservice/news-us.htm)

    * [Environmental Responsibility We don't just preach environmentalism...](https://www.owayo.com/productservice/environmental_responsibility-us.htm)
    
* more [Contact](https://www.owayo.com/productservice/contact-us.htm)

    Shopping Cart
    
    Your shopping cart is empty.

    [My Account](#) [Log out of](#)   Log in

Privacy Policy
==============

**We are pleased about your visit to our website and your interest in our company. Protecting your privacy is very important to us. We will provide you with detailed information on the handling of your data.**  

**I. Name and address of the controller**  
The controller as defined in the General Data Protection Regulation and other national data protection laws of the member states, as well as other provisions under data protection laws is:  
  
owayo, Inc.  
Telephone: +49 (0) 941 890 5500  
[\[email protected\]](https://www.owayo.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)  
www.owayo.com  

**II. Name and address of the data protection officer**

The data protection officer of the controller is:  
  
Michael Schindler  
Landshuter Str. 6  
D-93047 Regensburg  
[\[email protected\]](https://www.owayo.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)  
www.owayo.de

**III. General information concerning data processing**  
**1\. Scope of the processing of personal data**

As a rule, we only process personal data of our users if this is necessary to provide a functional website and our content and services. The processing of the personal data of our users generally takes place only with their consent. An exception applies in cases where the prior obtaining of consent is not possible for actual reasons and the processing is permitted by statutory regulations.

**2\. Legal basis for the processing of personal data**

Should we obtain the consent of the data subject for the processing of personal data, Article 6 Paragraph 1 Letter a) GDPR forms the legal basis for this.  
When processing personal data which is necessary to fulfil a contract where the contracting party is the data subject, Article 6 Paragraph 1 Letter b) GDPR forms the legal basis for this. This also applies to processing which is necessary to carry out pre-contractual measures. Should processing of personal data be necessary to fulfil a legal obligation which our company is subject to, Article 6 Paragraph 1 Letter c) GDFPR forms the legal basis for this. In case that vital interests of the data subject or of another natural person make the processing of personal data necessary, Article 6 Paragraph 1 Letter d) GDPR forms the legal basis for this.  
  
Should the processing be necessary in order to safeguard a legitimate interest of our company or of a third party and should the interests, basic rights and basic freedoms of the data subject not outweigh our legitimate interest, Article 6 Paragraph 1 Letter f) forms the legal basis of the processing.

**3\. Data deletion and duration of the saving**

The personal data of the data subject will be deleted or blocked, once the purpose of the saving no longer applies. Saving can take place beyond this time, if this was provided for by the European or national legislator in EU directives, laws or other regulations to which the controller is subject. The data will also be blocked or deleted if a saving period prescribed by the named norms expires, unless it is necessary to continue saving the data in order to conclude or fulfil a contract.

**IV. Provision of the website and creation of logfiles**  
**1\. Description and scope of the data processing**

Each time our Internet site is accessed, our system automatically records data and information from the accessing computer. During this process, the following data is gathered:  
  
(1) Information concerning the browser type and version used  
(2) The operating system of the user  
(3) The Internet service provider of the user  
(4) The IP address of the user  
(5) Date and time of the access  
(6) Websites from which the system of the user accesses our Internet site  
(7) Websites which are accessed by the system of the user via our website  
  
The data is also saved in the logfiles of our system. This data is not saved together with other personal data of the user.

**2\. Legal basis for the data processing**

The legal basis for the temporary saving of the data and the logfiles is Article 6 Paragraph 1 Letter f) GDPR.

**3\. Purpose of the data processing**

The temporary saving of the IP address by the system is necessary to deliver the website to the computer of the user. For this purpose, the IP address of the user must remain saved for the duration of the session.  
The saving in logfiles takes place in order to ensure the functionality of the website. In addition, the data allows us to optimize the website and ensure the security of our IT systems. The data is not evaluated for marketing purposes during this process.  
  
These purposes also represent our legitimate interest in the data processing in accordance with Article 6 Paragraph 1 Letter f) GDPR.

**4\. Duration of the saving**

The data will be deleted, once it is no longer necessary for the purpose for which it was gathered. In case of the recording of the data in order to provide the website, this is the case once the respective session has come to an end.  
  
In case of the saving of the data in logfiles, this is the case after a maximum of seven days. It is possible for the data to be saved beyond this period. In such a case, the IT addresses of the user will be deleted or disguised, so that it is no longer possible to assign this to the accessing client.

**5\. Right of objection and correction**

The recording of the data to provide the website and the saving of the data in logfiles is essential for the operation of the Internet site. As a result, the user does not have a right of objection.

**V. Use of cookies**  
**1\. Description and scope of the data processing**

Our website uses cookies. Cookies are text files which are saved in or by the Internet browser on the computer system of the user. Should a user access a website, a cookie can be saved in the operating system of the user. This cookie contains a character sequence, which enables a clear identification of the browser next time the website is accessed.  
  
We use cookies in order to make our website more user friendly.  
Certain elements of our Internet site require the accessing browser to also be identified following a change of site.  
Thereby the following data is saved and transferred in the cookies:  
  
(1) Language settings  
(2) Items in a shopping basket  
(3) Login information  
  
On our website, we also use cookies which enable an analysis of the surfing behaviour of the users. In this way, the following data can be transferred:  
  
(1) Search terms entered  
(2) Frequency of site access  
(3) Use of website functions  
  
The data of the users which is gathered in this way is pseudonymised by means of technical precautions. Therefore, it is no longer possible to assign the data to the accessing user. The data is not saved together with other personal data of the users.  
  
When accessing our website, the user is informed of the use of cookies for analysis purposes by means of an info banner and referred to this data protection declaration. During this process, information is provided as to how the saving of cookies can be prevented in the browser settings.

**2\. 2. Legal basis for the data processing**

The legal basis for the processing of personal data using cookies is Article 6 Paragraph 1 Letter f) GDPR.

**3\. Purpose of the data processing**

The purpose of the use of technically necessary cookies is to simplify the use of websites for the users. Certain functions of our Internet site cannot be provided without the use of cookies. For these, it is necessary for the browser to be recognized again after a change of site. For the following applications, we require cookies:  
  
(1) Shopping basket  
(2) Implementation of language settings  
(3) Marking of search terms  
  
The user data gathered by means of the technically necessary cookies is not used to create user profiles.  
  
The purpose of the use of the analysis cookies is to improve the quality of our website and its content. By means of the analysis cookies, we are informed of how the website is used and therefore we can constantly optimize our service.  
  
These purposes also represent our legitimate interest in the processing of personal data in accordance with Article 6 Paragraph 1 Letter f) GDPR.

**4\. Duration of the saving, right of objection and correction**

Cookies are saved on the computer of the user and are transferred by this to our site. Therefore, you as the user have full control over the use of cookies. By changing the settings in your Internet browser, you can de-activate or restrict the transfer of cookies. Cookies which have already been saved can be deleted at any time. This can also take place in automated form. Should cookies be de-activated for our website, it may be the case that certain functions of the website cannot be fully used.

**VI. Newsletter**  
**1\. Description and scope of the data processing**

Should you purchase goods or services on our Internet site and should you deposit your email address with us, this can then be used by us in order to send a newsletter. In such a case, only direct advertising for similar products or services of ours will be sent via the newsletter.  
On our website, it is possible to subscribe to a free-of-charge newsletter. During the registration for the newsletter, the following data is transferred to us:  
  
(1) Email address  
(2) Gender  
(3) First name  
(4) Last name  
  
The following data is also gathered during the registration:  
  
(1) IP address of the accessing computer  
(2) Date and time of the registration  
  
For the processing of the data, your consent is obtained during the registration process and you are referred to this data protection declaration.  
  
No data is disclosed to third parties in connection with the data processing for the sending of newsletters. The data is only used in order to send the newsletter.

**2\. Legal basis for the data processing**

The legal basis for the processing of the data following the registration for the newsletter by the user is Article 6 Paragraph 1 Letter a) GDPR, should the consent of the user be present.  
  
The legal basis for the sending of the newsletter following a purchase of goods or services is § 7 Paragraph 3 of the German Law against Unfair Competition (UWG).

**3\. Purpose of the data processing**

The purpose of the gathering of the email address of the user is the delivery of the newsletter.

**4\. Duration of the saving**

The data will be deleted, once it is no longer necessary for the purpose for which it was gathered. The email address of the user will however remain saved for as long as the newsletter subscription is active.

**5\. Right of objection and correction**

The subscription to the newsletter can be terminated by the user concerned at any time. For this purpose, a relevant link can be found in each newsletter.

**VII. Registration in the 3D configurator**  
**1\. Description and scope of the data processing**

On our Internet site, we offer our users the option of registering by providing personal data. During this process, the data is entered in to an entry mask, transferred to us and saved. The data is not disclosed to third parties. The following data is gathered during the registration process:  
  
(1) User name  
(2) Password  
(3) Email address  
  
In addition, the following data is saved at the time of the registration:  
  
(1) Date and time of the registration  
(2) Search terms entered  
(3) Date and time of the most recent login  
  
In the course of the registration process, the consent of the user to the processing of this data is obtained.

**2\. Legal basis for the data processing**

The legal basis for the processing of the data is Article 6 Paragraph 1 Letter a) GDPR, should the consent of the user be present.  
  
Should the purpose of the registration be the fulfilment of a contract where the contracting party is the user or the performance of pre-contractual measures, the additional legal basis for the processing of the data is Article 6 Paragraph 1 Letter b) GDPR.

**3\. Purpose of the data processing**

Registration of the user is necessary in order to fulfil a contract with the user or to carry out pre-contractual measures.  
  
The user has the option of saving various designs via our 3D configurator.

**4\. Duration of the saving**

The data will be deleted, once it is no longer necessary for the purpose for which it was gathered.  
This is then the case during the registration process in order to fulfil a contract or perform pre-contractual measures if the data is no longer necessary to perform the contract. Also following conclusion of the contract, it may be necessary to save personal data of the contracting partner in order to comply with contractual or statutory obligations.

**5\. Right of objection and correction**

As a user, you can cancel the registration at any time. You can have the data relating to you which has been saved altered at any time.  
  
In order to have the deletion carried out, you should send an email to [\[email protected\]](https://www.owayo.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) and request that your account data be deleted.  
  
Should the data be necessary in order to fulfil a contract or carry out pre-contractual measures, it is only possible to prematurely delete the data if contractual or statutory obligations do not prevent this.

**VIII. Registration in the shopping basket**  
**1\. Description and scope of the data processing**

On our Internet site, we offer our users the option of registering by providing personal data. During this process, the data is entered in to an entry mask, transferred to us and saved. The data is not disclosed to third parties. The following data is gathered during the registration process:  
  
(1) Name  
(2) Email address  
(3) Telephone number  
(4) Address  
(5) Company name  
(6) tax ID number  
(7) Deviating invoice address (if applicable) At the time of the registration, the following data is also saved:  
  
(1) Date and time of the registration  
  
In the course of the registration process, the consent of the user to the processing of this data is obtained.

**2\. Legal basis for the data processing**

The legal basis for the processing of the data is Article 6 Paragraph 1 Letter a) GDPR, should the consent of the user be present.  
  
Should the purpose of the registration be the fulfilment of a contract where the contracting party is the user or the performance of pre-contractual measures, the additional legal basis for the processing of the data is Article 6 Paragraph 1 Letter b) GDPR.

**3\. Purpose of the data processing**

Registration of the user is necessary in order to fulfil a contract with the user or to carry out pre-contractual measures.  
  
The user has the option of purchasing individual sports clothing via our Internet site.

**4\. Duration of the saving**

The data will be deleted, once it is no longer necessary for the purpose for which it was gathered.  
This is then the case during the registration process in order to fulfil a contract or perform pre-contractual measures if the data is no longer necessary to perform the contract. Also following conclusion of the contract, it may be necessary to save personal data of the contracting partner in order to comply with contractual or statutory obligations.

**5\. Right of objection and correction**

As a user, you can cancel the registration at any time. You can have the data relating to you which has been saved altered at any time.  
  
In order to have the deletion carried out, you should send an email to [\[email protected\]](https://www.owayo.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) and request that your shopping basket data be deleted.  
  
Should the data be necessary in order to fulfil a contract or carry out pre-contractual measures, it is only possible to prematurely delete the data if contractual or statutory obligations do not prevent this.

**IX. Disclosure of personal data to third parties**  
**1\. Shipping companies**  
**a) Description and scope of the disclosure of the data**  

In the course of the delivery, we pass personal data onto the engaged shipping company, DHL or FedEx. During this process, the following data is passed on:  
  
(1) Name  
(2) Address  
(3) Telephone number  
(4) E-mail Address

**b) Legal basis for the disclosure**

The data is only disclosed in order to fulfil the contract where the contracting party is the user, therefore the legal basis is Article 6 Paragraph 1 Letter b) GDPR.

**c) Purpose of the data disclosure**

The disclosure of the personal data of the contracting partner is necessary in order to fulfil a contract with him or her or to carry out pre-contractual measures.

**d) Duration of the disclosure**

The disclosure comes to an end, once this is no longer necessary to perform the contract. Also following conclusion of the contract, it may be necessary to pass on personal data of the contracting partner in order to comply with contractual or statutory obligations.

**e) Right of objection and correction**

As a user, you have the option of objecting to the disclosure of the personal data. You can have the data relating to you which has been saved altered at any time.  
Should the data be necessary in order to fulfil a contract or carry out pre-contractual measures, it is only possible to prematurely delete or block the data if contractual or statutory obligations do not prevent the deletion or blocking.

**2\. Banks**  
**a) Description and scope of the disclosure of the data**

During the course of processing of payments, we pass on personal data to Commerzbank and HSBC. During this process, the following data is passed on:  
  
(1) Name  
(2) Account details

**b) Legal basis for the disclosure**

The data is only disclosed in order to fulfil the contract where the contracting party is the user, therefore the legal basis is Article 6 Paragraph 1 Letter b) GDPR.

**c) Purpose of the data disclosure**

The disclosure of the personal data of the contracting partner is necessary in order to fulfil a contract with him or her or to carry out pre-contractual measures.

**d) Duration of the disclosure**

The disclosure comes to an end, once this is no longer necessary to perform the contract. Also following conclusion of the contract, it may be necessary to pass on personal data of the contracting partner in order to comply with contractual or statutory obligations.

**e) Right of objection and correction**

As a user, you have the option of objecting to the disclosure of the personal data. You can have the data relating to you which has been saved altered at any time.  
Should the data be necessary in order to fulfil a contract or carry out pre-contractual measures, it is only possible to prematurely delete or block the data if contractual or statutory obligations do not prevent the deletion or blocking.

**3\. Europa Inkasso**  
**a) Description and scope of the disclosure of the data**

In the course of collection of outstanding sums, we pass the data on to Europa Inkasso. During this process, the following data is passed on:  
  
(1) Name  
(2) Address  
(3) Telephone number  
(4) Email address  
(5) Receipts for outstanding sums

**b) Legal basis for the disclosure**

The data is only disclosed in order to fulfil the contract where the contracting party is the user, therefore the legal basis is Article 6 Paragraph 1 Letter b) GDPR.

**c) Purpose of the data disclosure**

The disclosure of the personal data of the contracting partner is necessary in order to fulfil a contract with him or her or to carry out pre-contractual measures.

**d) Duration of the disclosure**

The disclosure comes to an end, once this is no longer necessary to perform the contract. Also following conclusion of the contract, it may be necessary to pass on personal data of the contracting partner in order to comply with contractual or statutory obligations.

**e) Right of objection and correction**

As a user, you have the option of objecting to the disclosure of the personal data. You can have the data relating to you which has been saved altered at any time.  
Should the data be necessary in order to fulfil a contract or carry out pre-contractual measures, it is only possible to prematurely delete or block the data if contractual or statutory obligations do not prevent the deletion or blocking.

**4\. Other third parties**

No transfer, processing or use of the data you have provided to us will take place for advertising and marketing purposes.

**X. Contact form and email contact**  
**1\. Description and scope of the data processing**

Our Internet site contains a contact form, which can be used to get in touch with us electronically. Should a user make use of this option, the data entered into the entry mask is transferred to us and saved. This data includes:  
  
(1) Last name  
(2) First name  
(3) Address (if applicable)  
(4) Company or association (if applicable)  
(5) Email address  
(6) Telephone number (if applicable)  
(7) Message  
  
At the time of sending of the message, the following data is also saved:  
  
(1) Date and time of the registration  
  
For the processing of the data, your consent is obtained during the sending process and you are referred to this data protection declaration.  
  
Alternatively, you can get in touch with us via the email address provided. In this case, the personal data of the user which is sent with the email will be saved.  
  
No data will be passed on to third parties during this process. The data is only used in order to process the conversation.

**2\. Legal basis for the data processing**

The legal basis for the processing of the data is Article 6 Paragraph 1 Letter a) GDPR, should the consent of the user be present.  
  
The legal basis for the processing of the data which is transferred when sending an email is Article 6 Paragraph 1 Letter f) GDPR. Should the purpose of the email contact be the conclusion of a contract, the additional legal basis for the processing is Article 6 Paragraph 1 Letter b) GDPR.

**3\. Purpose of the data processing**

The sole purpose of the processing of the personal data from the entry mask is the processing of the contact initiation. In case of contact by email, this also represents the necessary legitimate interest in the processing of the data.  
The purpose of the other personal data which is processed during the sending process is the prevention of misuse of the contact form and ensuring the security of our IT systems.

**4\. Duration of the saving**

The data will be deleted, once it is no longer necessary for the purpose for which it was gathered. For the personal data from the entry mask of the contact form and the personal data sent by email, this is the case once the respective conversation with the user is closed. The conversation is closed once it can be assumed from the circumstances that the matter at hand has been finally clarified.  
  
The additional personal data gathered during the sending process is deleted at the latest after a period of seven days.

**5\. Right of objection and correction**

At all times, the user has the option of revoking his or her consent to the processing of the personal data. Should the user get in touch with us by email, he or she can object to the saving of his or her personal data at any time. In such a case, the conversation cannot be continued.  
  
A description follows concerning how the revocation of the consent and the objection to the saving are enabled.  
  
In such a case, all personal data which was saved in the course of the contact initiation will be deleted.

**XI. Sample service**  
**1\. Description and scope of the data processing**

Our Internet site contains a contact form for the ordering of visual samples, which can be used to get in touch with us electronically. Should a user make use of this option, the data entered into the entry mask is transferred to us and saved. This data includes:  
  
(1) Last name  
(2) First name  
(3) Address  
(4) Company or association (if applicable)  
(5) Email address  
(6) Telephone number  
(7) List of visual samples ordered  
  
At the time of sending of the ordering of visual samples, the following data is also saved:  
  
(1) Date and time of the registration  
  
For the processing of the data, your consent is obtained during the sending process and you are referred to this data protection declaration.  
  
In the course of the delivery of the samples, we pass personal data onto the engaged shipping company, DHL or FedEx. The scope and duration of the disclosure of the data are listed in chapter IX of this data protection declaration.

**2\. Legal basis for the data processing**

The legal basis for the processing of the data is Article 6 Paragraph 1 Letter a) GDPR, should the consent of the user be present.  
  
The legal basis for the processing of the data which is transferred when sending an email is Article 6 Paragraph 1 Letter f) GDPR. Should the purpose of the email contact be the conclusion of a contract, the additional legal basis for the processing is Article 6 Paragraph 1 Letter b) GDPR.

**3\. Purpose of the data processing**

The sole purpose of the processing of the personal data from the entry mask is the processing of the ordering of the samples.  
The purpose of the other personal data which is processed during the sending process is the prevention of misuse of the sample service and ensuring the security of our IT systems.

**4\. Duration of the saving**

The data will be deleted, once it is no longer necessary for the purpose for which it was gathered. For the personal data from the entry mask of the sample service, this is the case once the respective conversation with the user is closed. The conversation is closed once it can be assumed from the circumstances that the matter at hand has been finally clarified.  
  
The additional personal data gathered during the sending process is deleted at the latest after a period of seven days.

**5\. Right of objection and correction**

At all times, the user has the option of revoking his or her consent to the processing of the personal data. Should the user get in touch with us by email, he or she can object to the saving of his or her personal data at any time. In such a case, the conversation cannot be continued.  
  
A description follows concerning how the revocation of the consent and the objection to the saving are enabled.  
  
In such a case, all personal data which was saved in the course of the contact initiation will be deleted.

**XII. Offer service**  
**1\. Description and scope of the data processing**

Our Internet site contains an offer service, which can be used to get in touch with us electronically. Should a user make use of this option, the data entered into the entry mask is transferred to us and saved. This data includes:  
  
(1) Last name  
(2) First name  
(3) Address (if applicable)  
(4) Company or association (if applicable)  
(5) Email address  
(6) Telephone number (if applicable)  
(7) Products and quantities which should be issued for an offer  
  
At the time of sending of the form, the following data is also saved:  
  
(1) Date and time of the registration  
  
For the processing of the data, your consent is obtained during the sending process and you are referred to this data protection declaration.  
  
No data will be passed on to third parties during this process. The data is only used in order to process the conversation.

**2\. Legal basis for the data processing**

The legal basis for the processing of the data is Article 6 Paragraph 1 Letter a) GDPR, should the consent of the user be present.  
  
The legal basis for the processing of the data which is transferred when sending an email is Article 6 Paragraph 1 Letter f) GDPR. Should the purpose of the email contact be the conclusion of a contract, the additional legal basis for the processing is Article 6 Paragraph 1 Letter b) GDPR.

**3\. Purpose of the data processing**

The sole purpose of the processing of the personal data from the entry mask is the processing of the contact initiation. The purpose of the other personal data which is processed during the sending process is the prevention of misuse of the contact form and ensuring the security of our IT systems.

**4\. Duration of the saving**

The data will be deleted, once it is no longer necessary for the purpose for which it was gathered. For the personal data from the entry mask of the offer service, this is the case once the respective conversation with the user is closed. The conversation is closed once it can be assumed from the circumstances that the matter at hand has been finally clarified.  
  
The additional personal data gathered during the sending process is deleted at the latest after a period of seven days.

**5\. Right of objection and correction**

At all times, the user has the option of revoking his or her consent to the processing of the personal data. In such a case, the conversation cannot be continued.  
  
A description follows concerning how the revocation of the consent and the objection to the saving are enabled.  
  
In such a case, all personal data which was saved in the course of the contact initiation will be deleted.

**XIII. Google Analytics**

The body responsible for the processing has integrated the Google Analytics components (with anonymisation function) on this Internet site. Google Analytics is a web analysis service. Web analysis is the gathering, collection and evaluation of data concerning the behaviour of visitors to Internet sites. Amongst others, a web analysis service records data concerning from what Internet site a data subject came across an Internet site (so-called referrer), which subpages of the Internet site have been accessed or how often and for what duration a subpage was visited. A web analysis service is primarily used to optimize an Internet site and for a cost-benefit analysis in relation to Internet advertising.  
  
The operating company of the Google Analytics components is Google Inc, 1600 Amphitheatre Pkwy, Mountain View, CA 94043-1351, USA.  
  
The body responsible uses the "\_gat.\_anonymizeIp“ extension for the web analysis via Google Analytics. By means of this extension, the IP address of the Internet connection of the data subject is shortened and anonymised by Google, should the Internet sites be accessed from a Member State of the European Union or another Member State of the European Economic Area.  
  
The purpose of the Google Analytics components is to analyse the user traffic on our Internet site. Amongst others, Google uses the data which is acquired in order to evaluate the use of our Internet sites, to compile online reports for us which state the activities on our Internet sites and to provide other services connected to the use of our Internet site.  
  
Google Analytics sets a cookie on the IT system of the data subject. An explanation of what cookies are is provided above. By means of the setting of the cookie, Google is able to analyse the use of our Internet site. By means of each accessing of the individual pages of this Internet site which is operated by the body responsible for the processing and into which a Google Analytics component was integrated, the Internet browser on the IT system of the data subject is automatically instructed by the respective Google Analytics components to transfer data to Google for the purpose of the online analysis. In the course of this technical process, Google is informed of personal data, such as the IP address of the data subject, which enables Google amongst others to trace the origin of the visitors and clicks and to subsequently carry out commission billing.  
  
By means of the cookie, personal information, such as the time of access, the location from which an access originated and the frequency of the visits to our Internet site by the data subject is saved. Each time our Internet sites are visited, this personal data, including your IP address of the Internet connection used by the data subject, is transferred to Google in the USA. This personal data is saved by Google in the USA. Google may pass this personal data gathered through the technical procedure on to third parties in certain cases.  
  
The data subject can prevent the setting of cookies by our Internet site, as set out above at any time by setting the Internet browser used accordingly and thereby permanently objecting to the setting of cookies. Such a setting of the Internet browser used would also prevent Google setting a cookie on the IT system of the data subject. In addition, a cookie which has already been set by Google Analytics can be deleted at any time via the Internet browser or other software programs.  
  
In addition, the data subject has the option to object to the recording of the data generated by Google Analytics which relates to the use of this Internet site and the processing of this data by Google and to prevent such actions. In order to do so, the data subject needs to download and install a browser add on via the following link: [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en). This browser add on informs Google Analytics via JavaScript that no data and information concerning the visits to Internet sites may be transferred to Google Analytics. The installation of the browser add on is considered by Google to represent an objection. Should the IT system of the data subject be subsequently deleted, formatted or re-installed, the data subject needs to install the browser add on again in order to de-activate Google Analytics. Should the browser add on be de-installed or de-activated by the data subject or another person under his or her control, it is possible to re-install or re-activate the browser add on.  
  
Further information and the applicable data protection provisions of Google can be accessed at [https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en) and [https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/gb.html](https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/gb.html). A more detailed explanation of Google Analytics can be found via this link: [https://marketingplatform.google.com/about/](https://marketingplatform.google.com/about/).

**XIV. Use of social media plugins of Facebook**

Due to our legitimate interest in the analysis, optimisation and operation of our online service (in accordance with Article 6 Paragraph 1 Letter f) GDPR), this website uses the Facebook plugin, which is operated by Facebook Inc (1 Hacker Way, Menlo Park, California 94025, USA). The plugins can be recognized from the Facebook logo and the "like" and "share" buttons in the Facebook colors (blue and white). Information concerning all Facebook plugins can be found via the following link: [https://developers.facebook.com/docs/plugins/?locale=en\_US](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/plugins/?locale=en_US)  
  
Facebook Inc complies with European data protection laws and is certified under the Privacy Shield: [https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt0000000GnywAAC&status=Active](https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt0000000GnywAAC&status=Active)  
  
The plugin establishes a direct connection between your browser and the Facebook servers. The website operator has no control over the nature and extend of the data which the plugin transfers to the servers of Facebook Inc. Information in this respect can be found at: [https://www.facebook.com/help/186325668085084](https://www.facebook.com/help/186325668085084)  
  
The plugin informs Facebook Inc that you have visited this website as a user. During this process, your IP address may be saved. Should you be logged into your Facebook whilst visiting this website, the named information will be combined with this.  
  
Should you use the functions of the plugin, for example by sharing a comment or clicking on "like", the relevant information will also be transferred to Facebook Inc.  
Should you wish to prevent Facebook Inc combining this data with your Facebook account, you need to log out of Facebook before visiting this website and delete the saved cookies. Via your Facebook profile, you can carry out additional settings in relation to data processing for advertising purposes or object to the use of your data for advertising purposes. You can access the settings here:  
  
• Profile settings at Facebook: [https://www.facebook.com/login.php?next=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.facebook.com%2Fads%2Fpreferences%2F%3Fentry\_product%3Dad\_settings\_screen](https://www.facebook.com/login.php?next=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.facebook.com%2Fads%2Fpreferences%2F%3Fentry_product%3Dad_settings_screen)  
• Cookie de-activation page of the American website: [http://optout.aboutads.info/?lang=EN&c=2#!%2F](http://optout.aboutads.info/?lang=EN&c=2#!%2F)  
• Cookie de-activation page of the European website: [http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!%2F](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!%2F)  
  
The data protection regulations of Facebook inform you for what purpose and to what extent Facebook gathers, uses and processes data, as well as your settings options in order to protect your private sphere. You can find these here: [https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/)

**XV. Twitter ("tweet button")**<

We use the short messaging service on the technical platform and the services of Twitter Inc, 1355 Market Street, Suite 900, San Francisco, CA 94103 USA. The body responsible for the data processing of persons who live outside of the USA is the Twitter International Company, One Cumberland Place, Fenian Street, Dublin 2 D02 AX07, Ireland.  
  
We wish to point out that you are solely responsible for the use of the Twitter short messaging service and its functions which is provided here. This applies to the use of the interactive functions in particular (for example share, rate).

**1\. Data processed by Twitter:**

Information concerning the data which is processed by Twitter and the purposes for which the data is used can be found in the data protection declaration of Twitter: [https://twitter.com/en/privacy](https://twitter.com/en/privacy)  
  
Twitter Inc has undertaken to comply with the principles of the EU-US Privacy Shield. More information in this respect can be found at: [https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt0000000TORzAAO&status=Active](https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt0000000TORzAAO&status=Active)  
  
owayo has no influence over the type and scope of the data processed by Twitter, the type of processing and the use or disclosure of this data to third parties. It also has no effective way of monitoring this.  
  
By means of the use of Twitter, your personal data will be recorded, transferred, saved, disclosed and used by Twitter, and will be transferred to the USA, Ireland and any other country in which Twitter is present and saved and used there, regardless of where your place of residence is located.  
  
Thereby Twitter processes your data which is provided voluntarily on the one hand, such as your name and user name, email address, telephone address or the contacts in your address book, should you upload or synchronise this.  
  
On the other hand, Twitter also evaluates the content shared by you as to what topics interest you, saves and processes confidential messages which you send to other users and can determine your location on the basis of GPS date, information concerning cable free networks or via your IP address, in order to provide you with advertising or other content.  
  
For the evaluation, Twitter Inc may use tools such as Twitter or Google Analytics. owayo has no influence over the use of such tools by Twitter Inc and has also not been informed of their potential use. Should such types of tools be used by Twitter Inc for the account of owayo, owayo has neither engaged nor signed off such a service and has not supported this in any other way. In addition, the data gathered during the analysis will not be provided to it. Merely specified non-personal information concerning the tweet activities, such as the number of profile or link clicks by a specified tweet can be viewed by owayo via its account. In addition, owayo has no means of preventing or suspending the use of such tools in its Twitter account.  
  
Finally, Twitter is also informed if, for example, you view content even if you have not set up an account. This so-called "log data" may include the IP address, the browser type, the operating system, information concerning the previous website accessed and the sites accessed by you, your location, your mobile phone provider, the end device used by you (including device and application ID), the search terms used by you and cookie information.  
  
Via Twitter buttons or Twitter widgets integrated into websites and the use of cookies, it is possible for Twitter to record your visits to these websites and allocate these to your Twitter profile. On the basis of this data, content or advertising can be provided to you in a targeted manner.  
  
As Twitter Inc is a non-european provider which only has a European presence in Ireland, this is not subject to German data protection regulations by its own account. For example, this affects your right to information or the blocking or deletion of data or the option of objecting for the use of data for advertising purposes.  
  
You have the option of limiting the processing of your data in the general settings of your Twitter account and under the point "data protection and security". In addition, in the case of mobile devices (smartphones, tablet computers) you can limit the access by Twitter to contact and calendar data, photos, location data etc. in the settings options of the respective device. However, this depends on the operating system used.  
  
Further information in relation to these points can be found on the following Twitter support sites: [https://help.twitter.com/en/safety-and-security/twitter-privacy-settings](https://help.twitter.com/en/safety-and-security/twitter-privacy-settings)  

Here, you can find out how to view your data which is stored by Twitter: [https://help.twitter.com/en/managing-your-account/accessing-your-twitter-data](https://help.twitter.com/en/managing-your-account/accessing-your-twitter-data)  
  
Here, you can find information as to how Twitter can trace your person: [https://twitter.com/your\_twitter\_data](https://twitter.com/your_twitter_data)  
  
You can find information concerning the available personalization and data protection settings options here (with further references): [https://twitter.com/personalization](https://twitter.com/personalisation)  
  
You also have to option of requesting information via the Twitter data protection form or the archive requests: [https://help.twitter.com/forms/privacy](https://help.twitter.com/forms/privacy)  
  
[https://help.twitter.com/en/managing-your-account/how-to-download-your-twitter-archive](https://help.twitter.com/en/managing-your-account/how-to-download-your-twitter-archive)

**XVI. Instagram (integrated pictures)**

Functions and content of the service Instagram, provided by Instagram Inc, 1601 Willow Road, Menlo Park, CA, 94025, USA may be integrated into our online service. For example, this can include content such as pictures, videos or texts and buttons, by means of which users can share content of this online service within Instagram. Should the users be members of the platform Instagram, Instagram can assign the access to the content and functions referred to above to the Instagram accounts of the users. Data protection declaration of Instagram: [https://help.instagram.com/519522125107875](https://help.instagram.com/519522125107875).

**XVII. Rights of the data subject**

Should your personal data be processed, you are a data subject under the GDPR and have the following rights in relation to the controller:

**1\. Right of information**

You can request confirmation from the controller as to whether personal data relating to you is processed by us.  
  
Should such processing take place, you can request the following information from the controller:  
  
(1) the purposes for which the personal data is processed;  
  
(2) the categories of personal data which are processed;  
  
(3) the recipients or categories of recipients to whom the personal data relating to you has been disclosed or will be disclosed;  
  
(4) the planned duration of the saving of the personal data relating to you or, should concrete information not be possible in this respect, the criteria for determining the duration of the saving;  
  
(5) the existence of a right to have the personal data relating to you corrected or deleted, a right to have the processing by the controller restricted and a right to raise an objection to this processing;  
  
(6) the existence of a right to complain to a supervisory authority;  
  
(7) all available information concerning the origin of the data, should the personal data not be obtained from the data subject;  
  
(8) the existence of automated decision making, including profiling in accordance with Article 22 Paragraphs 1 and 4 GDPR and, at least in these cases, detailed information concerning the involved logic and the breadth and intended effects of such processing for the data subject. You have the right to request information as to whether the personal data relating to you is transferred to a third country or an international organisation. In this respect, you can request to be notified of the suitable guarantees in connection with the transfer in accordance with Article 46 GDPR.

**2\. Right of rectification**

You have the right of rectification and/or completion in relation to the controller, should the personal data being processed which relates to you be incorrect or incomplete. The controller must carry out the correction immediately.

**3\. Right of restriction**

Under the following conditions, you can request that the processing of the personal data relating to you be restricted:  
  
(1) if you dispute the correctness of the personal data relating to you for a period of time which enables the controller to check the correctness of the personal data;  
  
(2) if the processing is unlawful and you reject the deletion of the personal data and instead you request that the use of the personal data be restricted;  
  
(3) if the controller no longer requires the personal data for the purposes of the processing, however you require it in order to assert, exercise or defend legal claims, or  
  
(4) if you have raised an objection to the processing in accordance with Article 21 Paragraph 1 GDPR and it is not yet clear whether the legitimate reasons of the controller outweigh your reasons. Should the processing of the personal data relating to you have been restricted, this data, apart from its saving, may only be processed with your consent or for the assertion, exercising or defense of legal claims, to protect the rights of another natural or legal person or for reasons connected to the public interest of the EU or a Member State.  
  
Should the processing be restricted in accordance with the conditions above, you will be informed by the controller before the restriction is lifted.

**4\. Right of erasure**  
**a) Deletion obligation**

You can request that the controller immediately deletes the personal data relating to you and the controller is obliged to immediately delete this data, should one of the following reasons be present:  
  
(1) the personal data relating to you is no longer necessary for the purpose for which it was gathered or otherwise processed;  
  
(2) you revoke your consent on which the processing was based in accordance with Article 6 Paragraph 1 Letter a) or Article 9 Paragraph 2 Letter a) GDPR and no other legal basis for the processing is present;  
  
(3) you raise an objection to the processing in accordance with Article 21 Paragraph 1 GDPR and no legitimate reasons for the processing which take priority are present or you raise an objection to the processing in accordance with Article 21 Paragraph 2 GDPR;  
  
(4) the personal data relating to you has been processed unlawfully;  
  
(5) the deletion of the personal data is necessary to fulfil a legal obligation under EU law or the laws of the Member States to which the controller is subject;  
  
(6) the personal data relating to you was gathered in relation to the services offered by the information company in accordance with Article 8 Paragraph 1 GDPR.

**b) Information to third parties**

Should the controller have made the personal data relating to you public and should it be obliged to delete this in accordance with Article 17 Paragraph 1 GDPR, then taking the available technology and implementation costs into account, it will take reasonable measures, also of a technical nature, in order to inform the responsible body which processes the personal data that you as a data subject have requested the deletion of all links to this personal data or the deletion of all copies or reproductions of this personal data.

**c) Exceptions**

The right of erasure does not apply, should the processing be necessary:  
  
(1) to exercise the right of freedom of expression of one's opinion or information;  
  
(2) to fulfil a legal obligation which makes the processing necessary according to EU law or the laws of the Member States to which the controller is subject or in order to fulfil a task which is in the public interest or which took place in the course of the exercising of official powers which were transferred to the controller;  
  
(3) for reasons connected to the public interest in the area of public health in accordance with Article 9 Paragraph 2 Letter h) and Letter i), as well as Article 9 Paragraph 3 GDPR;  
  
(4) for archiving purposes, scientific or historical research purposes or for statistical purposes which are in the public interest in accordance with Article 89 Paragraph 1 GDPR, should the right named under Section a) be expected to make the attainment of the objectives of this processing impossible or be expected to significantly impair this, or  
  
(5) in order to assert, exercise or defend legal claims.

**5\. Right of notification**

Should you have claimed the right of rectification, erasure or restriction of the processing against the controller, it is obliged to notify all recipients to whom the personal data relating to you was disclosed of this rectification or deletion of the data or processing restriction, unless this is shown to be impossible or would lead to disproportionately high expenses.  
  
You have the right to be informed of these recipients by the controller.

**6\. Right of data portability**

You have the right to receive the personal data which you have provided to the controller in a structured, up-to-date and machine readable format. You also have the right to transfer this data to another responsible body without being hindered by the controller to whom the personal data was provided, should:  
  
(1) the processing take place with your consent in accordance with Article 6 Paragraph 1 Letter a) GDPR or Article 9 Paragraph 2 Letter a) GDPR or be based on a contract in accordance with Article 6 Paragraph 1 Letter b) GDPR and  
  
(2) the processing take place with the assistance of automated procedures. When exercising this right, you also have the right to have the personal data relating to you transferred directly from one controller to another responsible body, should this be possible in technical terms. Freedoms and rights of other persons may not be impaired as a result.  
  
The right of data portability does not apply to the processing of personal data which is necessary in order to fulfil a task which is in the public interest or which takes place in the course of the exercising of public powers which have been transferred to the controller.

**7\. Right of objection**

For reasons connected to your specific situation, you have the right at any time to raise an objection to the processing of the personal data which relates to you which takes place in accordance with Article 6 Paragraph 1 Letter e) or f) GDPR; this also applies to any profiling which is based on these provisions.  
  
The controller will no longer process the personal data relating to you, unless it can prove mandatory protectable reasons for the processing which outweigh your interests, rights and freedoms or if the purpose of the processing is the assertion, exercising or defense of legal claims.  
  
Should the personal data relating to you be processed in order to carry out direct advertising, you have the right to raise an objection at any time against the processing of the personal data relating to you for the purposes of such advertising; this also applies to the profiling, should it be connected to such direct advertising.  
  
Should you object to the processing for purposes connected to direct advertising, the personal data relating to you will no longer be processed for these purposes.  
  
Regardless of Directive 2002/58/EC, you have the option of exercising your right of objection in connection with the use of services of the information company by means of automated procedures, where technical specifications are used.

**8\. Right to revoke the declaration of consent under data protection laws**

You have the right to revoke your declaration of consent under data protection laws at any time. The lawfulness of the processing which took place prior to the issuing of the revocation of consent is not affected.

**9\. Automated decision making in individual cases, including profiling**

You have the right not to be subjected to a decision which is based exclusively on automated processing, including profiling, which has legal effect on you or significantly affects you in a similar manner. This does not apply, should the decision:  
  
(1) be necessary in order to conclude or fulfil a contract between yourself and the controller;  
  
(2) be permitted under legal regulations of the EU or the Member States to which the controller is subject and these legal regulations contain reasonable measures to safeguard your rights and freedoms, as well as your legitimate interests, or  
  
(3) take place with your express consent.  
  
However, these decisions may not be based on special categories of personal data under Article 9 Paragraph 1 GDPR, unless Article 9 Paragraph 2 Letter a) or Letter g) applies and reasonable measures have been taken to protect the rights and freedoms, as well as your legitimate interests.  
  
In relation to the cases named in (1) and (3), the controller will take reasonable measures to protect the rights and freedoms and your legitimate interests, where as a minimum this includes the right to have a person intervene on the part of the controller, the right to set out one's own opinion and the right to contest the decision.

**10\. Right to complain to a supervisory authority**

Regardless of any legal remedies elsewhere under administrative laws or through a court, you have the right to complain to a supervisory authority, in particular in the Member State of your place of residence, your place of work or the location of the alleged breach, should you be of the opinion that the processing of the personal data relating to you breaches the GDPR. The supervisory authority to which the complaint was submitted will inform the complainant of the status and results of the claim, including the option of legal remedy before a court in accordance with Article 78 GDPR.

As of: February 2021

owayo® custom sports®

Sports

Strengths

About owayo

Contact

Select Country

© 2024 owayo GmbH. All rights reserved
